Spark a revolution!
Spark: A Space Tail is a adventure, animation,
comedy film directed by Aaron Woodley.
Spark, a teenage monkey and his friends, Chunk and Vix, are on a mission to
regain Planet Bana - a kingdom overtaken by the evil overlord Zhong.
Vix (voice), played by Jessica Biel.
The Queen (voice), played by Hilary Swank.
Bananny (voice), played by Susan Sarandon.
Spark (voice), played by Jace Norman.
The Captain (voice), played by Patrick Stewart.
Koko (voice), played by Athena Karkanis.
Spark (known as Spark: A Space Tail in the United States) is a 2016 animated science fiction adventure comedy film written and directed by
Aaron Woodley, and featuring the voices of Jessica Biel, Hilary Swank, Susan Sarandon, Patrick Stewart, Jace Norman and Alan C.
The film premiered on April 22, 2016, at the Toronto
Animation Arts Festival International.
It was released on April 14, 2017, in the United States by Open Road Films with distribution sold by
Double Dutch International in all international markets except China and South Korea.
Spark received mostly negative reviews, and was a major box-office
bomb, earning only $1 million on a $40 million budget.
The film explores themes of black hole, anthropomorphism, space, planet, monkey.
The tone is lighthearted and thought_provoking.